Finding Aid for International Board on Books for Young People
Clarke Historical Library
Dossiers of Award Nominees, 1984-1985, 1998, 2016
International Board on Books for Young People.
13.5 cubic ft. (in 20 boxes, 1 Oversized folder)
MSS.
The collection includes dossiers of international nominees for author and illustrator awards.
Clarke Historical Library, Central Michigan University
Acc#many
International Board on Books for Young People, Dossiers of Award Nominees are open for research.
Organizational History:
IBBY (the International Board on Books for Young People) is a non-profit organization which represents an international network of people who are committed to bring books and children together. Founded in Zurich (Switzerland) in 1953, it is today composed of more than 60 National Sections all over the world. The organization’s mission includes: promoting international understanding through children’s books; giving children everywhere the opportunity to have access to books with high literary and artistic standards; encouraging the publication and distribution of quality children’s books, especially in developing countries; providing support and training for those involved with children and children’s literature; and stimulating research and scholarly works in the field of children’s literature.
Among its activities are its biennial Hans Christian Andersen Awards, often called the “Little Nobel Prize”, which are presented to an author and an illustrator, living at the time of the recognition, whose complete works have made a lasting contribution to children’s literature. The Author’s Award has been given since 1956 and the Illustrator’s Award since 1966.
Established in 1986, the IBBY-Asahi Reading Promotion Award is given annually to a group or an institution which, by its outstanding activities, is judged to be making a lasting contribution to reading promotion programs for children and young people.
The IBBY Honor List is a biennial selection of outstanding, recently published books, honoring writers, illustrators and translators from IBBY member countries. The list includes the best in children’s literature from each country, recommended as suitable for publication throughout the world.
Since 1967 ICBD (International Children’s Book Day), which usually occurs around Hans Christian Andersen’s birthday of April 2, has been celebrated to inspire a love of reading and to call attention to children’s books. Each year a different National Section of IBBY is the international sponsor of ICBD, deciding upon a theme, prominent author, and illustrator to write a message to the world’s children and design a poster. Promotions, activities, and special events occur during the whole week.
Other activities include IBBY seminars and workshops (since 1985), a quarterly journal called the Bookbird, and the Centre of Books for Disabled Young People (since 1985). The Centre offers information, consultation, and documentation services, and is now a division of the Institute of Special Education at the University of Oslo (Norway).
Arrangement is by accession number, authors, illustrators, alphabetical by name.
The Clarke Historical Library purchased the books which were nominated for the Hans Christian Andersen Illustrator’s and Author’s Awards. The dossiers of the nominees were included with the books. The dossiers include biographical information on nominees and some photographs, examples of their art or writing, with some translations dating from various years, marked in the Box and Folder Listing as undated for practical purposes. A folder of organizational materials about IBBY, taken from its website complete the collection. The collection is ongoing. From 2014 forward accessions includes CDs and a flashdrive. As much as possible the contents of these media storage devices is print off and added to the collection to avoid future access difficulties.
Subjects:
International Board on Books for Young People.; Illustrators.; Children's literature--Awards.; Children's literature--Illustrations--Awards.
- International Board on Books for Young People, Dossiers of Award Nominees
  - Organizational Materials,2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Alexandrino, Helena,undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Atxaga, Bernardo (2 folders),undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Auer, Martin,undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Balog, Zvonimir,undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Beake, Lesley,undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Bigel, Paul (2 folders),undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Boie, Kirstin (2 folders),undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Bond, Ruskin,undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Cao Wenxuan,undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Chambers, Aidan,undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Coll, Ivar da,undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Cooper, Susan,undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Coran, Pierre,undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Dacosta, Luísa,undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Dayioğlu, Gülten (6 folders),undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Dickinson, Peter,undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Dros, Imme,undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Duríčková, Mária,undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Egli, Werner J.,undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Ewo, Jon,undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Farias, Juan (3 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Fine, Anne,undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Gaardner, Jostein,undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Haller, Bent,undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Helgadóttir, Gurùn (2 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Huovi, Hennele,undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Ishii, Momoko,undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, İzgü Muzaffer,undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Jensen, Louis (2 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Johansen, Hanna,undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Kallioniemi, Tuula (4 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Kanzawa, Toshiko,undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Kondoleon, Manos (2 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Lee, Dennis,undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Lindgren, Barbro,undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Loizou, Maro (2 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Lowry, Lois (2 folders),undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Machado, Ana Maria (3 folders),undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Magnea, frá Kelifum,undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Mahy, Margaret,undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Makarovič, Svetlana,undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Moeyaert, Bart (2 folders),undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Montes, Graciela (4 folders),undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Morgenstern, Susie,undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Nanetti, Angela,undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Nozière, Jean-Paul,undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Paljetak, Luko,undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Prochazkova, Iva,undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Reuter, Bjarne (2 folders),undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Rocha, Ruth (3 folders),undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Rúfus, Milan,undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Santos, Joel Rufino dos,undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Sato, Satoru,undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Schubieger, Jürg,undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Škrinjarić, Sunčana,undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Soares, Luisa Ducla,undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Stahuljak, Višnja,undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Stark, Ulf,undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Torrado, António,undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Uličiansky, Ján,undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Uspenskeii, E. (Eduard)undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Van Leeuwen, Joke,undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Vangheli, Spiridon (2 folders),undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Vieira, Alice,undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Waddell, Martin (Catherine Sefton) (2 folders),undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Wahl, Mats,undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Welsh, Renate,undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Wolf, Ema (3 folders),undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Yousefi, Mohammed Reza,undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominees, Zei, Alki,undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Áslaug Jónsdóttir,undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Berner, Rotraut Susanne,undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Brøgger, Lilian,undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Browne, Anthony,undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Bruna, Dick (3 folders),undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Calatayud, Miguel,undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Carrier, Roch,undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Castanha, Marilda,undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Cayatte, Henrique,undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Cho, Shinta,undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Delioğlu, Mustafa,undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Diodorov, Boris,undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Doyle, Brian,undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Dumas, Philippe,undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Eidrigevicius, Stasys,undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Ekman, Fam,undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Gál, László,undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Grähs, Gunna,undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Hilb, Nora,undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Hughes, Shirley,undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Job, Cvijeta,undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Joshi, Jagdishundated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Karrebaek, Dorte,undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Kaufmann, Agelika,undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Keil, Maria,undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Kyritsopoulous, Alexis,undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Lumme, Lena,undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Lynch, Patrick James,undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Moser, Erwin,undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Nine, Carlos,undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Paterson, Katherine,undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Psarafti, Litsa (2 folders),undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Queirós, Bartolomeu Campos,undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Raissi-Volanaki, Tatiana,undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Schroeder, Binette,undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Sigrun Eldjarn,undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Sollie, Andre,undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Stark, Ulf,undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Stupica, Marija Lucija,undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Tibo, Gilles,undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Wikland, Ilon,undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Wilkón, Józef (2 folders),undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Wilsdorf, Anne,undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominees, Young, Ed,undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous: Giganti fiamminghi -Flemish giants- Vlaamse reuzen,undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous: Register of German authors and illustrators,undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Almond, David,undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Desplechin, Marie,undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Doyle, Brian,undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, El Maadoul, Fatima,undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Ferro, Beatriz,undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, French, Jackie,undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Härtling, Peter,undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Helgadóttir, Gudrún,undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Kuijer, Guus,undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Lindgren, Barbro,undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Lilius, Irmelin Sandman,undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Litričin-Dunic, Dragana,undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Mayer-Skumanz, Lena,undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Navrátil, Ján,undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Prap, Lila,undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Procházková, Iva,undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Provoost, Anne,undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pulcheriou, Kika,undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Queirós, Bartolomeu Campos,undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Qin, Wenjun,undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Ratiu, Iului,undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Reuter, Bjarne,undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Schubiger, Jürg,undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Tanikawa, Shutaro,undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Thompson, Kate,undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Bajusová, Olga,undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Bajer, Jutta,undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Binder, Hannes,undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Born, Adolf,undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Brøgger, Lilian,undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Çinaroğlu, Ayla,undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Crowther, Kitty,undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, De Oliveira, Rui,undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Erikkson, Eva,undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Erkman, Nazanundated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Fitzpatrick, Marie-Louise,undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Fuentes, Marico Gómez Morin,undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Grobler, Piet,undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Hayashi, Akiko,undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Innocenti, Roberto,undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Isol [Misenta, Marisol],undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Junakovíc, Svjetlan,undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Papatsarouchas, Vassilis,undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Pieńkowski, Jan,undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Ponti, Claude,undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Pratt, Pierre,undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Talvitie, Virpi,undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Tan, Shaun,undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Tjong-Khing, Thé,undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Wofsgruber, Linda,undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous:Czech Republic lists of authors and illustrators,undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous:re: Romanians author Iului Ratiu and illustrator Stan Done,undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Oversized Folder, [Part of] the Dossier of Author’s Award Nominee- Sato, Satoru,undated (Folder 1)
  - CDs (2) Authors and Illustrators,2012 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Fleischman, Paul,2012 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Hoher, Franz,2012 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Kerim, Silvia (folder 1 of 5),2012 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Kerim, Silvia (folder 2 of 5),2012 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Kerim, Silvia (folder 3 of 5),2012 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Kerim, Silvia (folder 4 of 5),2012 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Kerim, Silvia (folder 5 of 5),2012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Mattingley, Christobel (folder 1 of 3),2012 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Mattingley, Christobel (folder 2 of 3),2012 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Mattingley, Christobel (folder 3 of 3),2012 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Mourlevat, Jean Claude,2012 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Nopola, Sinikka and Tiinae,2012 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Paz, Agustin Fernandez (folder 1 of 2),2012 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Paz, Agustin Fernandez (folder 2 of 2),2012 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pelz, Monika (folder 1 of 4),2012 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pelz, Monika (folder 2 of 4),2012 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pelz, Monika (folder 3 of 4),2012 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pelz, Monika (folder 4 of 4),2012 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pitzorno, Bianca,2012 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Pullman, Philip,2012 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Rsumovic, Ljubivoje,2012 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Sortland, Bjorn,2012 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Sortland, Bjørn,2012 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Dossiers of Author's Award Nominee, Wynne-Jones, Tim,2012 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Ballester, Arnal,2012 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Baniasadi, Mohammad Ali,2012 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Bernasconi, Pablo,2012 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Burningham, John,2012 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Galeron, Henri,2012 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Graham, Bob,2012 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Habinger, Renate,2012 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Joos, Louis,2012 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Jorish, Stéphane,2012 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Modovan, Valeria,2012 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Paegle, Anita,2012 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Rashka, Chris,2012 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Schärer, Kathrin,2012 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Sottler, Alenka,2012 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Spirin, Gennady,2012 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Torseter, Øyvind,2012 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Zabala, Javier,2012 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Dossiers of Illustrator's Award Nominee, Zivkovic, Dobrosav Bob,2012 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - List of Award Winners, Authors, 1956-2014; Illustrators, 1966-2014, 3 CDs,(CDs information printed, in following folders),2014 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Ar-Au,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Az-Be,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Ch-De,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Es-Fi,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Fr,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Ge,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Gr-Ir,1956-2014 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Ir,1956-2014 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, It-Ja,1956-2014 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Ne-No,1956-2014 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Po-Ru,1956-2014 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, Sl-Tu,1956-2014 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lists of Winners, By Country, UK-USA,1956-2014 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Andriat, Frank,2014 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Dossiers of Author’s Award Nominees: Colfer, Eoin,2014 (Box 10, Folder 8)